JOSHUA BOYD

21a, Barlow Moor Rd, Didsbury, Manchester, M20 6TN Mob: 07814166493
Email: josh@the-boyds.co.uk

PROFILE

I am a versatile and dedicated individual with a broad range of expertise encompassing many aspects of IT. My personal studies have afforded me with the opportunity to build and develop my ability and I have a strong background in Windows and Mac. I also have knowledge of Infrastructure and am interested in working in this area.

I am a hardworking and dedicated 1st line support technician with a passion for working in the IT industry. I have almost a year's experience of providing technical assistance with-in a phone support and customer facing environment. I have built up my knowledge to include aspects of Active Directory, MS Office, laptop/PC builds and basic network-telephony management. I am able to adapt and learn quickly, as I have shown so far during my time at HSS, and I am also capable of communicating effectively within the support team and with the clientele. I a confident in my ability to succeed within the Second line role and bring demonstrable value to any business I work with.

KEY SKILLS AND EXPERTISE

- Client/customer services and support
- Interpersonal skills
- Team work
- Excellent communication skills
- Stock Control and auditing
- Motivated and reliable

- Committed, adaptive and trusting
- Flexibility willing to learn and adapt
- Accuracy and performance
- Time-management
- Adobe creative cloud Lightroom and Photoshop
- Organisational skills

WORK EXPERIENCE

12/2018-Present First Line IT Service Technician, HSS Hire Head Office

- Provide effective IT support services across all clients both onsite and remotely through email, face-to-face and telephone.
- Ensure all incidents are closed within SLA
- Ensure that all installations are completed in a timely and professional manner and that deadlines are either achieved or exceeded
- Working with customers and internal teams to ensure operational and service excellence delivered and maintained.
- Maintaining IT equipment including computers, laptops, printers and mobile phones.
- Dealing with network and internet connectivity issues.
- Installing and updating security software and updates.
- Escalating unresolved issues to 2nd line Support Technicians when required
- Relaying complex problems or gueries to the Support Manager

04/2010-09/2018 Chef, Zinc Cafe, Bar & Grill, Abersoch

- Prepared and cooked food in a busy establishment, whilst supervising over kitchen on the Head Chefs days off
- Responsible for the ordering and control of stock for kitchen
- Dealt with issues with any food being returned from customer, whilst plating up and presenting dishes on pass
- Discussed and implemented new menu ideas with Head Chef

06/2010-04/2012 Asst. Bar Manager, Zinc Bar Abersoch

- Served alcoholic beverages, ordered and controlled the stock of the bar, cashed up the till and collected payments from customers utilising an electronic till
- Successfully hired and mentored new Employees, alongside the Manager whilst addressing any complaints and resolving problems with customers or staff

EDUCATION / PROFESSIONAL TRAINING

09/18-present	Currently studying following courses:
	• CompTIA A+ 220-1001
	• CompTIA A+ 220-1002
09/11-09/12	Completed and passed first year of BSc Computing.
09/09-07/11	Coleg Meirion-Dwyfor, Pwllheli
	Information Technology - D
	Double Award Business Studies - DE
09/07-07/09	Ysgol Botwnnog
	3 x B
	4 x C
	2 x D

REFERENCES AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST